上
Let's go!
-传给我 传给我 -我没看见
-I'm open, I'm open. -I don't see it!
-抓紧时间 -跑位
-Take your time! -Run!
-进攻 -上 上
-Run! -Go go!
-上 – 防守 防守
-Let's go! -Defense! Defense!
好样的
Come on man!
-紧逼防守 紧逼防守 -注意控球
-Hustle hustle! -Control that ball!
-波顿 传给我 -组织起来 上
-Bolton! I'm open! -Set it up! Let's go!
很好 上 移动 注意移动
All right let's go! Let's move! Let's move!
-注意穿插 -注意后面
-Watch the run in. -Watch the back door!
知道
Get it!
决赛上半场最终结果
That concludes the first half of play
西部高中骑士队以47比26
In our final game with the west high knights
领先卫冕冠军东部高中野猫队
Leading defending champion east high wildcats 47:26.
比赛还有16分钟
Sixteen minutes remain in the game.
好了 别管什么战术 好吗
All right! No more x's and o's. OK
忘掉记分板上的数字
Forget about the scoreboard
因为只有一个数字是重要的
Because here's a number that matters.
16 比赛还剩下16分钟 伙计们
Sixteen. There's 16 minutes left in this game, guys.
这个赛季也只剩下16分钟
There's only 16 minutes left in the season.
对于本队的毕业生来说...伙计们...
And for the seniors on this squad...guys...
你们也只能再能穿16分钟的野猫队服了
You've only got sixteen minutes left in a wildcat uniform.
好好把握吧
So make them count.
16分钟 团结一致
Sixteen minutes to be a team.
队长时间
Captains!
好了
All right.
兄弟们
Hey guys.
你们听到教练讲的了
Now you heard coach.
我们都将铭记接下来的16分钟
We're all gonna remember the next sixteen minutes
即使离开东部高中很久以后
For a long time after we leave east high.
此时不搏 更待何时
So it's now or never.
查德
Chad.
-什么队 -野猫队
-What team -Wildcats!
16 16 16分钟 争取胜利
Sixteen sixteen sixteen minutes left better get it done.
16 16 16分钟 整装待发
Sixteen sixteen sixteen more minutes get ready game on!
16 16 16分钟 时间紧迫
Sixteen sixteen sixteen minutes left running out of time.
16 16 16分钟 一触即发
Sixteen sixteen sixteen more minutes and it's on the line.
16 16 16分钟 争取胜利
Sixteen sixteen sixteen minutes left got to get it done.
16 16 16分钟 唯我独尊
Sixteen sixteen sixteen more minutes till we're number one!
W I L D 野猫队
W-I-L-D Wildcats!
围过来 快
Huddle up! Let's go!
W I L D 野猫队 加油 加油
W-I-L-D Wildcats! Come on come on.
准备好了吗
Ready
加油
Break!
W I L D 野猫队
W-I-L-D Wildcats! Now's the time.
低空运球 突破内线 投篮
Got to get it inside down low in the paint now shoot!
得分
Score!
-合作 -回防
-Gotta work together -Defense!
传我球
Give me the ball.
快速突破 保持控球 弧线划过三分线
Fast break keep the ball in control let it fly from downtown.
再得三分
Three more.
我们能做得更好
Show them we can do better.
加油 男孩们
Come on boys!
最后的决战 铭刻心中
The way we play tonight is what we leave behind.
叱诧赛场 唯我独尊
It all comes down to right now it's up to us.
-上 -团队合作
-Let's go! -So what are we gonna be.
所向披靡
T-E-A-M team!
全力出击 进攻
Gotta work it out turn it on.
最后一次 展现球技
This is the last time to get it right.
最后一晚 闪耀舞台
This is the last chance to make it our night.
我们使出 看家本领
We got to show what we're all about.
合作
Work together!
最后一场 赢取比分
This is the last chance to make our mark
篮坛史册 铭记我们
History will know who we are
巅峰之战 要打得完美
This is the last game so make it count it's now or never
-犯规 -天啊
-Hey! That's a foul! -Oh dear.
-还好吗 -加油 特洛伊
-You ok -Come on Troy!
兄弟们 上
Let's go buddy!
特洛伊
Troy
此刻我几乎无法呼吸
Right now I can hardly breathe
我坚信你能做到
Oh you can do it just know that I believe
这就是我所要的
And that's all I really need
-加油 -令我坚强
-Then come on -Make me strong
是时候 奋起直追
It's time to turn it up game on!
野猫队把对手撕碎 你们是最棒的
Wildcats gonna tear it up go wildcats we're number one
犯规
Foul!
-太好了 -好
-Yeah! -All right!
-什么 -好
-What -Yeah!
让我听到你的呐喊
Let me hear you say hey hey hey yeah
我被三人包夹 没办法投篮
I'm tripled-teamed. I can't get a shot off.
-你想怎么做 队长 -让火箭人上场
-What do you want to do，Captain -Let's put in rocket man.
火箭人
Rocket man
-特洛伊 还差2分...-我知道
-Troy you're two points away from...-I know.
-把球传给我就好 -好的
-Just get me the ball. -OK.
火箭人 过来 过来 火箭人 你上
Rocket man! Come on! Come on rocket man! You're in!
-过来 -快去
-Get in here! -Go!
-去啊 -快
-Let's go! -Move!
去去去 快去
Go go go! Move!
冷静点
Calm down OK
-好了 留意我 -比赛开始
-All right keep your eyes on me. -Game on!
最后一次 展现球技
This is the last time to get it right
最后一晚 闪耀舞台
This is the last chance to make it our night
我们使出 看家本领
We gotta show what we're all about team! Work together
最后一场 赢取比分
This is the last chance to make our mark
篮坛史册 铭记我们
History will know who we are
巅峰之战 要打得完美
This is the last game so make it count it's now or never
加油
Come on!
投篮
Shoot it!
赢了 我们赢了 老兄 你没事吧
We won dude! We won! You ok
这才是我们想要的
That's what I'm talking about. Yeah!
我推着呢
I'm pushing.
-你最好在推 -推着呢
-You better be pushing. -I'm pushing!
-用力推 -查德 小心树
-Push harder! -Chad tree!
家 甜蜜的家
Home sweet home.
-我在攒钱买新的燃油泵 -嗯 快点攒吧
-I'm saving for a new fuel pump. -Mm-hm. Save faster.
大点声 凯尔西
Hey turn it up Kelsi.
-你好吗 -好极了
-How you doing girl -I'm good!
-完美的回归 -谢谢
-Great comeback! -Thanks.
-当心尾巴 老兄 危险 -可不是吗
-Watch that tail. It's dangerous. -You know it!
-太棒了 我们赢了 -我以为他们追不回来呢
-Amazing!We won! -I didn’t think they’d come back.
-祝贺啊 小野猫 -谢谢 我帮你拿些吃的怎么样
-Congratulations!Wildcat!-Thanks. Can I fix you a plate
-我什么都要 -我们在庆祝吗
-I want one of everything! -Are we celebrating?
你好啊 硬汉
What's up hoops
-蝉联冠军 -是啊 谢谢
-Back-to-back champions! -Yeah thanks.
教练 阿尔伯克基大学还有空的储物柜吧
Coach got a couple of empty lockers at U of A
但愿不会空太久
Hopefully not for long.
查理 丹弗斯正适合打下个赛季
Charlie Danforth will suit up next season.
我坐前排座位就好
Front row seat will be fine.
我从你们身上看到了的团队精神
I tell you that teamwork I saw tonight your guys
为了助攻宁愿放弃最后投篮机会
That assists where you gave up the final shot
正是我要找的队员
That's the kind of players I'm looking for.
我们再见时你们就穿上红鹰队队服了吧
We're going to see you in red hawk uniforms
-一言为定 -祝你们好运
-Done deal. -Amen to that.
-去好好玩吧 -好的
-Go have some fun. -OK.
-祝贺你 特洛伊 -谢谢
-Congratulations Troy! -Hey! Thanks.
特洛伊 房子棒极了 你房间真酷
Hey Troy. Great house bro. Your room is way cool.
谢谢 你进了我房间吗
Thanks man. You were in my room
是啊 我还拍下来了 看
Well yeah. I just took a picture. Look.
-我想按同样的方式布置我的 -好
-I'm doing mine the same way. -Great.
我们今晚该好好逛逛
We should hang out tonight.
相互了解下
Get to know each other or something.
我得先去拿冠军奖杯
I just gotta grab the championship trophy
我忘在车里了
I left it in my truck.
-别累着 我去拿 -好
-Don't sweat it! I'm on it! -OK.
所以 又一个秘密基地啊
So another top-secret hiding place
你是第二个来这的女孩
You're the second girl I've had up here.
第一个是我妈妈
The first was my mom.
她上来是要抓我下去
She only climbed up here to get me down.
我很荣幸 这里很酷
Well I'm honored. This place is so cool.
我和我爸建的
Me and my dad built it.
阿尔伯克基大学的教练来了
Is that the coach from U of A down there?
-是啊 他来我家了 -是啊
-yeah. He's at my house. -Yeah.
真疯狂
Crazy.
我打赌 他已经在储物柜上贴上你名字了
I bet he's already got your name on a locker.
这是一直是我爸的梦想
It's always been my dad's dream.
我将去他母校就读了
Now I'm going to end up at his alma mater.
我真说出来了
Did I just say that
我妈妈和我自我出生以来
My mom and I have been talking about
就在聊斯坦福大学
Stanford pretty much since I was born.
你已经被录取了 太酷了
And you're already in. That's so cool.
不过她一直炫耀这事 太难为情了
Except she won't stop talking about it. It's embarrassing.
别这样 她以你为荣
Come on. She's proud of you.
我也为你自豪
I'm proud of you.
问题是斯坦福离这一千零五十...
The thing about Stanford is it's a thousand and fifty...
...五十三公里
...fifty-three miles from here.
我知道
I know.
突然觉得
It suddenly seems like
剩下的高中时光来的太快了
The rest of the school year is coming so fast.
是啊 我希望可以停止
Yeah. I wish it would all just stop.
至少慢下来
At least just slow down.
能否想象 丢失梦想
Can you imagine what would happen
将会暗淡无光
If we could have any dream
希望此刻 永被铭记
I'd wish this moment was ours to own it
直至永恒
and that it would never leave
感谢星辰
Then I would thank that star
让我们愿望成真
that made our wish come true
有你之处
'cause he knows that where you are
乃我之所
is where I should be too
此地
Right here
此刻
Right now
-此刻 -凝望着你
-Right now -I'm looking at you
我心所属
and my heart loves the view
-你乃一切 -一切
-'Cause you mean everything -Everything
此地
Right here
向卿起誓无论如何
I promise you somehow
无论如何一定会
Somehow we're gonna
再次相逢
Tomorrow can wait for some other day to be
此刻 只有你我
to be but right now there's you and me
重逢之日
Oh we know it's coming
必将来临
and it's coming fast
永生相伴
it's always you and me
珍惜每瞬
so let's make every second last
珍惜
Make it last
只因此地
'Cause right here
此刻
Right now
凝望着你
Yeah I'm looking at you
我心所属
and my heart loves the view
你乃一切
'cause you mean everything
此地
Right here
向卿起誓无论如何
I promise you somehow
重逢之日
That tomorrow can wait
必将来临
for some other day to be
此刻 只有你我
to be but right now there's you and me
-你和我 -你和我
-You and me -You and me
你和我
You and me
此刻 只有
But right now there's
你和我
You and me
这是海盗船舵吗
Is this a pirate's wheel
不是
No.
好可爱
Very cute.
我三年级开始就不和罗伯玩了
I haven't played with robo-rob since third grade.
-我叫罗伯 我是...-别弄坏了
-I'm robo-rob. I am...-Don't break him. Don't break him.
-那是查德的 -当然
-That's Chad's. -Sure it is.
这像在幼儿园
Now it's just like kindergarten.
特洛伊 客人们在等呢
Troy You have guests.
别让我再上去抓你下来
Don't make me come up there and get you again.
你好 盖比瑞拉
Hi Gabriella.
我们就下来 妈妈
We'll be right down mom.
我们不下去的话 她真的会上来的
She really will come up here if we don't go down.
那儿 向前开 好的向前
Right there right there. OK come on through.
安全通过
Come on. There you go.
靓 爆 了
你好 特洛伊
Hey Troy.
决赛什么时候
So when's the big game
昨天
Uh yesterday.
好吧 祝你好运
Oh well. Good luck.
哇...她真可爱
Wow...She's so sweet.
你是什么 我是说 你是谁
What are you I mean who are you
早上好 埃文斯小姐 我是缇安拉·高德
Good morning Ms. Evans. I'm Tiara Gold.
我从伦敦转校到东部高中
I transferred to east high from London
我看到公告板上
And I noticed on the board
你需要私人助理
You're in need of a personal assistant.
是啊 毕业考试 毕业舞会 毕业典礼
Yeah with finals prom graduation
需要有人处理我的约会和作业
I need someone tracking my appointments and assignments.
最重要的是我需要人对台词
Most important I need someone to run lines for the musical.
这是戏剧术语 为了...
That's a theater term for...
更好地理解角色 我明白
Learning your role. I understand.
第一二节课是科学和数学
It's best to keep science and math books together
把书放在一起比较好
Since those are first lessons of the day.
你怎么知道我的课程表
How do you know my schedule
我特意查了一下
I took the liberty of checking simply to make certain
我为你在课间准备了无脂 无泡 大豆拿铁咖啡
I'd have your nonfat no-foam soy latte ready for free period.
-加一袋糖了吗 -还是有机的
-One packet of sweetener -Organic of course.
每天早晨 我会把我的衣着电邮给你
I'll e-mail you my wardrobe choices
以防我们撞衫
Each morning so that our outfits won't clash.
如果你有橙色的衣服 扔掉吧
If you own any orange get rid of it.
顺便说下 喜欢你口音
By the way like the accent.
很...可爱
It's...sweet.
特洛伊 我的兄弟 我可以用你的储物柜吗
Troy my brother. Can I have your gym locker
-什么 -下周开始怎么样
-What -Like starting next week.
下赛季我说不定带领球队
I'll be running the team next season
这能帮我壮壮声威
And it'll help me out with the guys.
-是啊 我怎么没想到 – 我不知道
-Yeah why didn't I think of that -I don't know.
又要迟到了 回见 兄弟
Tardy again. Later bro!
你认真的吗
Are you serious
-那她呢...-你好
-What about her...-Hey.
好了 各位 坐好
All right everyone. Settle down.
我知道大家都为野猫队获得
I know we are all excited about our wildcats'
-大满贯而兴奋 -应该是蝉联冠军 达老师
-"Top-to-bottom" championships. -That would be "back-to-back." Miss D
不管怎么说都是件大喜事 做得好
Whatever the case it was a grand slam. Well done!
我们的学生会主席兼毕业年鉴主编
And our student body president and co-editor of the yearbook
泰勒·麦肯锡有重要通知
Taylor Mckessie has important announcements.
毕业班舞会委员会明天开会
Senior trip committee meets tomorrow
周四向毕业舞会委员会报告
And reports Thursday to prom committee
由玛莎主持 大家从她那里取票
Headed by Martha. Pick up your tickets from her.
今年的主题是"最后的华尔兹"
This year's theme is "the last waltz."
但是千万别最后拿票
But don't be last to pick up tickets.
毕业庆典委员会星期一集合
Graduation committee convenes Monday.
交照片最后期限是星期四
Picture deadline is Thursday
期末考试学习小组填补空挡
And finals study groups alternate with all of the above.
有问题吗
Questions
自助食堂午餐有什么特色菜
What's the lunch special in the cafeteria
纽约特色菜 其他人还有问题吗
New York deli. Anyone else
继续 夏培·埃文斯小姐
Moving on. Ms. Sharpay Evans
戏剧学会的四届会长
Four-term president of the drama club
春季音乐剧汇报
Spring musicale report.
每个人都忙于毕业舞会 期末考试
Well with prom finals everyone is so busy.
我想应该选些小型表演
I was thinking I'd select something modest to perform.
一场一个女人的独角戏如何
Perhaps even a one-woman show.
没人报名吗 凯尔西
A little light on the sign-ups Kelsi
不是 我们进行得很好
No. we're actually doing pretty well.
几乎整个教室的人都要参加
Well well well. Almost the entire homeroom.
多么鼓舞人心啊
How inspiring!
我非常乐于见到你们
I will happily see all of you
在课余时间讨论这场演出
at free period to discuss the show
并且我有个特别的通知
And to make a very special announcement.
我期末重考过两三次了
I'll be retaking my finals two or three times.
我几乎住进图书馆了
I'm moving into the library.
每天放学后我都要修理卡车
I'm working on my truck every day after school.
家政学期末考我要做5个菜
I've got five recipes for family science final.
我要编辑毕业班年鉴 所以不行
We've got a yearbook to edit so no.
对不起 老天
Sorry! Jeez.
我认为既然这是最后一场演出
I thought since it was the last show
每个人都会想参加
everyone would want to do it.
-你错了 -我们只是没有时间
-You're wrong. -We just don't have time.
大伙儿 听着 凯尔西是对的 我们应该参加
Hey. hey you guys listen up. Kelsi's right. We should do this.
这是我们最后的集体活动机会
This is our last chance to do something together.
我们所有人 真的很有意思
All of us. Something really fun.
太好啦
Oh yippee.
怎么样 野猫队的
So what do you say wildcats
不 我仍然不支持这做法
No I still don't think it's a good idea.
-伙计们 来吧 这是我们的最后一年 -特洛伊
-Guys come on! It's our senior year! -Troy.
我们都参加吧
We're all in this together.
这是我们的最后一年
This is our senior year.
我参加
I'm in.
什么
What
-会很有趣的 -太好了
-It will be fun. -Yes!
-真是的 -这要花多少时间
-Oh boy. -How much time will it take
是啊 还有这该死的表演是什么内容
Yeah. and what the heck is the show about
你 丹弗斯先生
You Mr. Danforth.
我
Me
春季音乐剧全都是关于你
The spring musicale is all about you.
打住 如果是关于我
Hold up. If it's about me
能不能把篮球还给我 可以吗
Then can I have my ball back Please
-是关于你们所有人 -走吧
-It's about all of you. -Go!
所有人参与创作
And all of you will create it.
一场你们在东部高中最后时光的演出
A show about your final days at east high.
我们将它命名为毕业季
We'll call it senior year.
真有才
Genius.
扮演一个角色很容易
Uh-uh-uh! Playing a role is easy
但是演你自己 是个挑战
But being yourself now that's a challenge.
达布斯老师 到底...
Miss Drbus exactly...
凯尔西作曲 瑞恩编舞
Kelsi will compose Ryan will choreograph
-我来导演 -谢谢
-And I will direct. -Thank you.
现在 我有重大消息宣布...
Now I have some very important news from...
...纽约茱莉亚学院
...the Juilliard school in New York City
美国一流的表演艺术大学
America's preeminent college for the performing arts.
东部高中史上第一次
And for the first time in east high history
茱莉亚学院考虑在你们四个中
Juilliard is considering four of you
挑选一个授予奖学金
For one available scholarship.
-夏培·埃文斯小姐 -我行李都打包了
-Miss Sharpay Evans. -I'm already packed.
-瑞恩·埃文斯先生 -舞蹈
-Mr. Ryan Evans. -Dance.
-凯尔西·尼尔森小姐 -什么 他们收到我的信了
-Miss Kelsi Nielsen. -What They got my letter
那是必然
They certainly did.
最后 特洛伊·波顿先生
And lastly Mr. Troy Bolton.
什么
What
茱莉亚学院会派代表来观看我们的表演
Juilliard will be sending representatives to observe our show.
祝四个申请人好运
So good luck to our four applicants.
不错 不错 伙计们 这很有趣
Yeah nice. Nice guys. That's pretty funny.
那么...谁做的恶作剧
So...who's the big comedian
-是哪里搞错了吗 -是的 我没有申请
-Is there something wrong -Yeah. Yeah I didn't apply.
我从来没听说过茱莉亚学院
I've never heard of Juilliard.
也许你没听说过 波顿先生
Well that may be Mr. Bolton
但很明显茱莉亚学院听说过你
But evidently Juilliard has heard of you.
既然你们参与创作 你们必须仔细考虑
And as you create this show you must dig deep
思考一下你们对未来的渴望和梦想
And think about your aspirations and dreams for the future.
请到舞台前排成一行
Line up downstage please.
从丹弗斯先生开始 请向前一步
Let's begin with Mr. Danforth. Step forward please.
你的未来
Your future.
很简单 上阿尔伯克基大学 一路投篮
It's easy. It's U of A. Hoops all the way.
-就是 -麦肯锡小姐
-Yeah. -Miss Mckessie.
我要成为美国总统
I'm going to be the president of the United States.
当然 我要先上完大学
I'm going to finish college first of course.
玛莎·考克斯 你迟到了
Martha Cox you're late.
对不起 达布斯老师
I'm sorry,Miss Drbus.
我只是想 也许我们还需要一些舞蹈演员
I just thought maybe we could use a few more dancers.
我觉得演出已经开始了
I feel a show coming on already!
波顿先生
Mr. Bolton.
-波顿先生 -什么事
-Mr. Bolton. -Hmm
-你的未来 -哦 是啊...
-Your future. -Oh yeah uh...
你知道...嗯...
You know...uh...
我在想...
I've been thinking about...
我建议 演出一场完美的毕业舞会
I think we should stage the perfect prom.
天啊 多可爱呐 我想要什么
Golly gee how adorable. What do I want
天哪 我不知道从何处开始
Gosh I wouldn't know where to begin.
但是我知道终点在哪儿
But I know where it ends.
中央舞台
Center stage.
单束聚光灯
A single spotlight.
巨大的遮檐上写着...
A huge marquee that reads...
请来一盘纽约熟食
New York deli platter please.
你这时候怎么还能想着吃的
How can you think about food at time like this
也许因为现在是午餐时间
Maybe because it's lunch time
不要腌黄瓜 要那个大块的苹果冻
No pickles. Better throw that big apple parfait in there.
好了 这场演出是我们最后一场 瑞恩
Ok, this show is our last shot, Ryan.
夏培的饭 谢谢
Sharpay's meal please. Thanks.
-给你 -饭不错
-Here you are. -That's great.
特洛伊装作对茱莉亚学院一无所知
Troy pretended to know nothing about Juilliard.
-得了吧 -我觉得他很惊讶
-Give me a break. -He seemed surprised to me.
歌剧院精灵用魔法投递了特洛伊的申请表吗
The theater fairy magically sent in Troy's application
演员没法儿唬弄我
Performers can't fool me.
他们虚伪 有野心 并且残忍
They're deceitful ambitious and ruthless.
-我们不是演员吗 -没错
-Aren't we performers -Exactly.
想象一切美梦成真
Imagine having everything we ever dreamed
-是否心动 -也许
-Don't you want it -Maybe
-试想将来 -一点
-Can't ya see it -Kinda
想象大学毕业 试镜之时 我做主角
Imagine first audition after college I get the lead
-有我的角色吗 -当然
-A part for me -Well of course
-对 没错 接着说 -你应该相信
-Yeah right keep talking -You gotta believe it
-你和我 所有的声望 -夏培和那谁
-You and I all the fame -Sharpay and what's-his-name
-听起来刺激吗 -诱人
-Sound exciting -Inviting
-那就开始吧 -说来听听
-Let's do it then -Listening
私人造型师 经纪人和广告
Personal stylist agent and a publicist
-那我的位置在哪里 -有你合作就能赢
-But where do I fit into this -With you we can win
-赢得角色 -野心要更大
-Win the part -Think bigger
-成为超级明星 -这个不赖
-Become superstars -That's better
还不明白吗 越大越好
Don't you see that bigger is better
越好就会越大
and better is bigger
只有一点儿永远不够 不 不 不
A little bit it is never enough no no no
你不想这些全部都要
Don't you want it all
你想要 你知道你想要
You want it you know that you want it
名声 财富 还有更多
The fame and the fortune and more
你全部都想要
You want it all
你想要 你知道你想要
You want it you know that you want it
你的门上会有属于自己的星
You gotta have your star on the door
你要全世界 什么都不能少
You want the world nothing less
所有名流雅士还有报刊
all the glam and the press
只会给你最好的评价
only giving you the best reviews
-说吧 -我全部都要
-Say it! -I want it all
我要 我要 我要
I want it I want it want it
我的名字在卡耐基音乐厅被光线照亮
My name in lights at Carnegie hall
我全部都要
I want it all
-你没看见吗 -看见了
-Can't you see it -Yeah
大家都喜欢我
They're gonna love me
是爱我们
I mean us
红地毯 玫瑰花 后台等待的人群
Red carpet rose bouquets crowd waiting backstage
我是她同伴 请别阻拦我 我不是狗仔队
I'm with her don't stop me I'm not the paparazzi
邀请 起立喝彩
Invitations standing ovations
-杂志 -是的 请
-Magazines -Yes please
摇身一变成名流
Gonna be celebrities
照片 歌迷俱乐部 给人们他们所爱
Photographs fan club give the people what they love
-你现在很兴奋 -我喜欢
-Now you're excited -I like it
-现在就动手 -我爱你
-Let's do it then -I love you!
时代广场 喷气式客机 续集赚更多
Times Square jetsetter sequels pay better
今天在纽约 明天就红遍全世界
New York today tomorrow the world
-票都售罄 -野心要更大
-Sold out shows -Think bigger
-获得奥斯卡奖的是...-这个不赖
-And the Oscar goes to...-That's better
你没看见越大越好 越好就越大
Don't ya see that bigger is better and better is bigger
一点儿永远都不够 不 不 不
A little bit is never enough no no no
我全部都要 我想要 想要 想要
I want it all I want it want it want it
名声 财富 还有更多
The fame and the fortune and more
我全部都要 我想要 想要 想要
I want it all I want it want it want it
我的门上会有属于我的星
I gotta have my star on the door
我要全世界 什么都不能少
I want the world nothing less
所有名流雅士和报刊
all the glam and the press
只会给我最好评价
only giving me the best reviews
我全部都要 我想要 想要 想要
I want it all I want it want it want it
无线城音乐厅 我全部都要
Radio city music hall we want it all
在聚光灯下 我们闪闪发光 看看我们是谁
Here in the spotlight we shine look at who we are
当百老汇知道你的名字
When Broadway knows your name
-别挡道 -你知道你是个明星
-Get out of the way! -You know that you're a star
噢 跳舞
Oh dance
-麦迪逊广场花园 -他们爱你
-Madison square garden! -They love you.
谢谢 谢谢大家
Thank you! Thank you all!
奥普拉来电
It's Oprah calling.
又来了
Again.
她想让你出演
She wants you on the show.
他们会给你回电话
They're going to get back to you.
-你知道自己开多快吗 -查德警官
-You know how fast you were going -Officer Chad!
是埃文斯小姐啊 你怎么样 跟着我
Hey it's Ms. Evans. How you doing Follow me.
我想要 我 我 我想要 想要
I want it I-I-I want it want it
我想要 我想要 我 我 我全部想要
I want it I want it I-I-I want it all yeah
我想要 我 我 我想要 想要
I want it I-I-I want it want it
-我想要 我 我 我想要 -我全部想要
-I want it I-I-I want it -I want it all
我将 哦 我将 我要 我必须 我要
I gotta ooh I gotta I want to I have to I want to
我想要 我想要 我必须拥有这些
I want it I want it I have to have it
我想要 我必须
I want it I have to
-我全部想要 -我想要 想要 想要
-I want it all -I want it want it want it
-名声 财富 还有更多 -我全部想要
-The fame and the fortune and more -I want it all
我想要 想要 想要
I want it want it want it
我的门上会有属于自己的星
I gotta have my star on the door
我要全世界 什么都不能少
I want the world nothing less
所有名流雅士和报刊
all the glam and the press
只会给我最好评价 我全部都要
only giving me the best reviews I want it all
巴黎 伦敦 罗马 多伦多
Paris London Rome Toronto
洛杉矶 悉尼 布宜诺斯艾利斯
L.A. Sydney Buenos Aires
东京 莫斯科 宝莱坞
Tokyo Moscow Bollywood
纽约城
New York city
我们全部...
We want it...
都要
all
非我们莫属 瑞恩
It's ours Ryan.
等一下 达老师说只有一份奖学金
Wait a minute. Miss D said that there's only one scholarship.
我们却有两个人
There's two of us.
我们是双胞胎 他们必须同时招收我们两个
We're twins. They're going to have to take us both.
听着 凯尔西总给特洛伊和盖比瑞拉最好的歌
Listen Kelsi always writes her best songs for Troy and Gabriella.
所以你来保证那些歌归我们
So you make certain we get those songs.
怎么拿
How
给她擦眼镜 买双深红色拖鞋
Polish her glasses buy her some ruby slippers
约她去毕业舞会
take her to prom.
我不知道
I don't know.
做就行了
Just do it.
-早 泰勒 -早 阳光美少女
-Hey Tay. -Morning Sunshine.
-你今天去彩排吗 -我有的选吗
-You going to rehearsals today -Uh do I have a choice
你把我们都拉进来
You got us into this.
我不明白 你不该忙演出的
I don't understand. You might not be here for the show.
告诉别人你申请斯坦福了吗
Told anyone you're up for Stanford's freshman honors
没有
No.
没准哪天你就会得到回信
You're gonna hear from them any day.
-喂 -泰勒 这种事都很花时间的
-Hello -Taylor these things take time.
-喂 -我现在需要你
-Hey. -I need you right away.
-什么 -抬头看
-What -Look up.
我要走了
I have to go.
明摆着 会被罚放学留校两周
This has two weeks detention written all over it.
玩得开心
Have fun.
我真的需要你帮忙
I really need your help.
你认为我应该穿哪一件
Which one do you think I should wear
为什么要选
Because
因为你会穿一件很漂亮的裙子
Because you're going to have a pretty dress
我不能给你丢面子
So I want to look right.
我从来没被邀请过去毕业舞会
I've never been asked to a prom
但是这听起来很像邀请
But this almost sounds like an invitation.
这一件
This one.
我从来没去过舞会 更不用说毕业舞会了
I've never been to a dance much less a prom.
但是我希望这是个良好开端
But I was hoping these might be a good start.
我们必须跳华尔兹吗
Do you think we're going to have to waltz
因为我不知道怎么跳
Because I have no idea how to do that.
我只记得小的时候 爸爸教过我
All I know is what my dad taught me when I was a little girl.
我站在他的脚上
I'd stand on his toes
他带着我在客厅里跳华尔兹
And he'd waltz me around the living room.
到这儿来 我带你跳
Come here. I'll show you.
-什么 -过来
-What -Come here.
我们在屋顶上
We're on the roof.
过来 你会喜欢的
Come here. You'll love it.
牵着手
Take my hand
深呼吸
Take a breath
贴着我
Pull me close
迈一步
and take one step
你的目光
keep your eyes
注视着我
locked on mine
随着音乐
And let the music
慢慢起舞
be your guide
-能否答应我 -现在 能否答应我
-Won't you promise me -Now won't you promise me
-你永不忘记 -我们一直跳下去
-That you'll never forget -We'll keep dancing
不管我们去哪儿 都一直跳下去
to keep dancing wherever we go next
不管我们去哪儿
Wherever we go next
寻寻觅觅
It's like catching lightning
与你相遇
the chances of finding
甚是不易
someone like you
万里挑一
It's one in a million
你我恋情
the chances of feeling
相连一起
The way we do
我们舞步轻盈
and with every step together
我们携手共进
We just keep on getting better
-能否共舞一曲 -能否共舞一曲
-So can I have this dance -Can I have this dance
能否共舞一曲
Can I have this dance
山不再高
No mountain's too high and
海不再阔
No ocean's too wide
无论相聚离别 舞蹈永不停息
'Cause together or not our dance won't stop
无论风霜雨雪...
Let it rain...
我们勿言放弃
Let it pours what we have is worth fighting for
深信你我天生一对
You know I believe that we were meant to be
寻寻觅觅 与你相遇
It's like catching lightning the chances of finding
甚是不易
someone like you
万里挑一 你我恋情
It's one in a million the chances of feeling
相连一起
the way we do
我们舞步轻盈
And with every step together
我们携手共进
We just keep on getting better
-能否共舞一曲 -能否共舞一曲
-So can I have this dance -Can I have this dance
能否共舞一曲
Can I have this dance
-能否共舞...-一曲
-Can I have...-this dance
能否共舞一曲
Can I have this dance
-你是同意了么 -我愿用世上的每一种语言
-So is that a yes -In every language.
来告诉你
We see ya
我同意
Yes.
快点儿
Oh come on!
我们的衣服呢
Where's our clothes
-火箭人 -原来在你们那儿
-Yo rocket man. -Oh there they are.
-不是想要我们的柜子么 -今天搬吧
-Thought you wanted our lockers. -It's moving day.
太棒了
Oh sweet.
-干得好 -谢了 伙计
-Good job. -Thanks man.
你来的太是时候了 波顿
Perfect timing Bolton.
我们不会轻易就把柜子给你们
We weren't just given these lockers.
这是我们努力得来的
We had to earn them.
好吧 好吧 谢了 伙计
Right. Right. Thanks man.
查德 密码是多少
Hey Chad what's the combo
是呀 密码是多少呀 伙计们
Yeah what's the combo guys
就像他说的 你们得通过努力得到
It's like he said. You got to earn them.
那是什么意思啊
What's that supposed to mean
伙计们 回来 你们什么意思呀
Hey guys! Come back. What are you talking about
-这不好玩 伙计们 -波顿 丹弗斯
-Not cool guys! -Hey Bolton! Danforth!
别玩了
Hey stop playing games!
这并不有趣 伙计们
This isn't funny guys!
查德 扔过来
Chad come on.
接到
I got it.
-快跑 离开这儿 -把衣服还我
-Let's go! Out! -Give me my clothes!
这并不好玩儿 伙计们
This isn't funny guys!
快把衣服还给我 老兄
Just give me my clothes man!
小心 借过
Look out. Coming through.
我新买的牛仔裤 我还得穿呢
Hey those are new jeans! I need those back!
抬手 二 三 四 五 六 七 八
Arms two three four five six seven eight.
你快把我逼疯了
You're really stressing me out.
我得喘口气 我不知道瑞恩正在干什么
I need to breathe. And I don't know what Ryan is doing.
在练那些娘娘腔的瑜伽动作
He's doing some kind of yoga fosse thing.
二 三 四...
Two three four...
你在干什么 六 七 八...
What're you doing six seven eight...
一 二 三 很好 五 六 七...
One two three great five six seven...
特洛伊 把衣服还我
Troy just give me my clothes!
-年鉴好素材 -快照相
-Yearbook opportunity. -Photo op.
笑一笑
Smile!
-您好 -胆子不小啊 先生们
-Hi. -Bold choice gentlemen.
我们必须有探索自身的勇气
We all must have the courage to discover ourselves.
然而 在东部高中
However at east high
我们得穿着衣服探索自身
We will discover ourselves whilst clothed.
但欢迎来到戏剧社和春季音乐会
But welcome to our drama club and our spring musicale.
没错 欢迎
Yeah welcome.
你们被留校时 正好剧务人员需要帮忙...
The stage crew can use your help during detention...
...粉刷背景
...painting sets.
给他们弄张褥单
Throw a sheet over them.
瑞恩
Ryan!
好吧 伙计们 我们从头再来一遍
Ok. All right guys let's go back up to the top.
杰森 过来帮把手
Jason why don't you come down here and help me out.
这油泵...
Fuel pump...
...正在存钱买了 如果因为忙着排练
...work in progress. If my truck falls apart
没空管车 它散架的话都怪你
Because I'm spending all my free time onstage it's your fault.
要不是为了你
You really think I'd be spending any time at all up there
我会把时间都花在舞台上么
If it wasn't for you
知道么 你该演出
You know what I do.
-什么 -你太出色了
-What -You're so good.
看你排练的时候 你沉醉其中
I watch you in rehearsals. You love it.
承认自己的心意又不丢脸
Why is that so hard for you to admit
对你承认并不难
It isn't to you.
但对我的父亲 对查德 是有点难
But to my dad To Chad Yeah it's a little hard.
不会的
It shouldn't be.
一谈起阿尔伯克基大学 他们就很开心
They're happy as long as we're all talking about U of A.
你选择斯坦福
You chose Stanford.
阿尔伯克基大学是我的选择
U of A was sort of chosen for me.
我从没跟别人谈过这些 但是...
I haven't talked to anybody about this but...
...我也收到其他学校的录取通知书
...I've had offers from other colleges.
-我真的用心了 -我懂了 特洛伊
-I'm really listening. -I get it Troy.
我也没下定决心
I still have decisions to make too.
决定什么
Like what
我就觉得听到你的声音了
I thought I heard you.
我刚才在里面做小吃
I was just making some snacks inside.
你们饿了么
Are you guys hungry
-我打扰到你们了 是吗 -只是随便聊聊 妈妈
-I interrupted something didn't I -Just talking mom.
-在谈家庭作业 -好吧
-Homework. -OK.
提到作业...来吧
Speaking about homework...come on.
我是开玩笑
I was joking.
是从奇克那儿拿的 小心点 很烫
It's compliments of Zeke. be careful they're still hot.
但他还不知道它们不见了
But he doesn't know they're gone yet.
所以你得吃掉这些罪证
So you have to eat the evidence.
和年鉴的编辑们亲热 真是太明智
Kissing up to the yearbook editors. Very smart move.
查德希望给自己开两页专栏
Chad's hoping for two pages on himself.
可能还有第三页 是留给他头发的
Maybe even a third page just for his hair.
事实就是事实
Hey what's right is right.
对了 顺便说一下
Hoops by the way
放学后能带我去挑身晚礼服么
Could you take me after school to check out that tuxedo
晚礼服 干什么用的
Tuxedo For what
为了毕业舞会
For prom.
亲爱的 如果你就这么邀请我的话
Honey if that's what you call an invitation
你还是和自己去吧
You'll be dancing with yourself.
-午餐时间到了 -快点 大家 快
-Yo Yo Yo. It's lunchtime. -Come on people. Go!
-准备好了么 -是的
-You ready -Yeah.
做就做到最好 伙计
It's now or never man.
园艺社赞助的
The garden club is rooting for you.
-好的 我这就去 -搞定她
-OK. I'm going in. -Go get her.
-特洛伊 我真的有点...-不行 现在就去
-Troy I really just...-No we're doing this now.
你在上面呆多久了
How long have you been up there
-发型不错 -别碰...
-Hair's great. -Don't...
我知道 我也听说了
I know. I heard that too.
-是的 很好 -是 好的
-Yes good. -Yes. OK.
轮到你了
Your turn.
我在想是否你能...
I was kind of wondering if you'd...
...和我一起去
...maybe go with me.
查德 菜谱上居然有金枪鱼 很好吃
Chad. They have tuna surprise on the menu. It's good.
真的很好吃
Really good.
伙计
Dude.
泰勒
Taylor.
我再要请你参加毕业舞会
Hey I'm asking you to prom.
抱歉 我没听清楚 这儿太吵了
I'm sorry I can't hear you because it's so loud.
-你听见了么 -没有
-Did you hear something -No.
-我也没听见 -大伙 打扰一下 打扰一下
-Neither did I. -OK excuse me. Excuse me everybody.
你在干什么...
What are you...
我的朋友有事要宣布
My friend has something to say.
泰勒·麦肯锡
Taylor Mckessie.
能邀请你做我毕业舞会上的舞伴么
Will you please be my date to the senior prom
很荣幸
I'd be honored.
伙计 我要去打会儿篮球了
Dude I need to go shoot some hoops or something.
你办到了 伙计
You nailed it! Man.
正式的约会来临
Guess now it's official
-不能退缩 不能胆怯 -绝不
-Can't back out can't back out -No
准备好了
Gettin' ready
只为今夜 今夜 今宵 今夜
for the night of nights the night of nights all right
-不要慌张 -慌张
-Don't panic -Panic
为了舞会 我们盛装打扮
Now do we have to dress up for the prom
伙计 我们别无选择
Dude I don't think we have the choice
盛装打扮 只为今夜
Yeah it's the night of all nights got to look just right
盛装打扮 吸引帅哥
Dressin' to impress the boys
传统 复古 或是嬉皮风格
Do I want classic or vintage or plaid
-照照镜子 -礼服太大
-Where's the mirror -I think this tux is too baggy
太小 都有损形象
too tight it makes me look weird
模仿明星 魅力四射
Should I go movie star glamorous
迷人 泼辣还是可爱
sassy or sweet
不知道 但这是为我量身定做
Don't know but no one better wear the same dress as me
我们的噩梦之夜
It's the night of our nightmares
我们的美梦之夜
It's the night of our dreams
太晚了 不能退缩
It's too late to back out of it
-化浓妆 做美容 -不知胸花是何物
-Hey makeovers massages -Don't know what a corsage is
用尽一生来等待
Been waiting all our lives for this
-这将是一个夜晚 -不能等待
-It's gonna be a night -Can't wait
-令人难忘的夜晚 -伙计
-to remember -Oh man
一起狂欢吧 好的
Come on now big fun all right
-这将是一个夜晚 -我猜是
-It's gonna be the night -I guess
-永不消逝的夜晚 -我们真幸运
-to last forever -Lucky us
我们永远永远永远不会忘记
We'll never ever ever forget
-准备好了 -准备好了
-Gettin' ready -Get ready
-准备 准备好了 -准备好了
-Get gettin' ready -Get ready
准备好了
Gettin' ready
准备 准备好了 出发
Get gettin' ready go
伙计 你在那儿呆了一个小时了
Hey you've been in there an hour, man.
我应选择什么发型
So what should I do with my hair
-我的剃须刀呢 -我喜欢它
-Where's my shaver -I love it
-我看上去就像服务生 -该弄蓬松么
-I look like a waiter -Should I fluff it
已经快迟到了
It's getting later already should be there
她的母亲打开了门 我的内心难以平静
Her mother opens the door I'm shakin' inside
他来了 正点到达
He's here it's time the hour's arrived
不知为何 她的父亲让我沮丧
Don't know why her father's starin' me down
钱包在哪 唇膏在哪 我手足无措
Where's my purse lip gloss Now I'm really freakin' out
从此以后 我的世界大不相同
Then something changes my world
最美丽的女孩就在我眼前
The most beautiful girl right in front of my eyes
这将是一个夜晚
It's gonna be a night
-令人难忘的夜晚 -一定没错
-to remember -That's for sure
来吧 一起狂欢 好的
Come on now big fun all right
-这将是一个夜晚 -就是今晚
-It's gonna be the night -Here tonight
-永不消逝的夜晚 -永远不会
-to last forever -Forever more
我们永远永远永远不会忘记
We'll never ever ever forget
伙计们 在这儿 伙计们
Guys right here. Guys!
那个女孩是谁 她真美丽
Who's that girl She's so fine
那个男孩是谁 我认不出
Who's that guy I don't recognize
那个女孩是谁 她很漂亮
Who's that girl She looks so good yeah
曾经被你忽视 现在请注意
Guess you never really noticed but you probably should
狂欢
big fun
-就在这个夜晚 -没错
-On the night of nights -All right
就在今夜 今宵今夜
The night of nights tonight
一起跳舞
Let's dance
就在今夜 我们一定会成功
On the night of nights you know we're gonna do it right
这将是一个 令人难忘的夜晚
It's gonna be a night to remember
这将是一个 永不消逝的夜晚
It's gonna be the night to last forever
这将是一个 令人难忘的夜晚
It's gonna be our night to remember
这将是一个 永不消逝的夜晚
It's gonna be the night to last forever
-这将是我们的夜晚 -你一定知道
-It's gonna be our night -You know it
-铭记于心 -直到永远
-to remember -for all time
-来吧 -一起狂欢
-Come on now -Big fun
-这将是一个夜晚 -我们非常喜欢
-It's gonna be the night -We love it
-不会消逝 -永远不会消逝
-to last forever -The rest of our lives
我们永远永远永远不会忘记
We'll never ever ever forget
这将是我们的夜晚
It's gonna be our night oh yeah
-一起来吧 -大声说
-All together -Say it loud
-大家一起来 -就是这样
-Come on now everyone -That's right
-这将是一个夜晚 -是个夜晚
-It's gonna be a night yeah -It's the night
-令人难忘的夜晚 -听听欢呼声
-to remember -Hear the crowd
永远永远永远
and never ever ever
永远永远永远永远永远
never ever ever never ever
永远永远不会被遗忘
never never forget
妙 妙极了 灯光
Bravo! Brava! Lights please!
凯尔西 音乐太美妙了
Kelsi splendid music.
瑞恩 舞蹈创意十足
Ryan your choreography is quite inventive.
-谢谢 -杰森
-Thank you. -And Jason
在剧院或者舞会不许吃口香糖
We do not chew gum in theatre or prom.
一会留下见我 灯光组需要帮忙
See me at detention. Lighting crew needs help.
大家干的太出色了
Excellent work everyone.
别忘了把服装放在架子上 明天见
Don't forget costumes on the rack. I will see you all tomorrow.
凯尔西正在为特洛伊和盖比瑞拉写着个非常好的东西
Kelsi's writing something amazing for Troy and Gabriella.
最多就是首歌曲
A song most likely.
去查查到底是什么 好了 去吧
Just find out what it is. Ok go.
小家伙 我刚才跳得好么 谢谢
Hi boi! How was I Thank you!
-特洛伊 干的漂亮 伙计 -伙计 快点走开
-Hey Troy good job man. -Dude stop doing that!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
看 夏培在那儿
Look there's Sharpay.
别说是我告诉你的
Now you didn't hear this from me
她暗恋你
But she has a secret crush on you.
暗恋我
A secret crush on me
-我应该和她谈谈么 -对
-Should I talk to her -Yeah.
好的
OK. All right.
萨拉先生
Mr. Zara.
不介意的话 叫我"火箭人"就可以了
Yo! You can call me "rocket man" if you want to.
真有肚量
How generous.
萨拉先生 既然你如此愿意登台
Mr. Zara since you have become such a dedicated presence
我就让你当替补演员吧 高德小姐
I'm making you an understudy. Miss Gold!
-你也是 -真不错
-You as well. -Nice.
太好了 伙计
All right dude.
入伙了
I'm in!
我要扮演"替补演员"了
I'm playing "the understudy."
-祝贺你 -对吧 怎么了
-Congrats. -That's right What's up
"替补演员"不是个角色 你这笨蛋
"Understudy" isn't a role you moron.
意思是主演们演不了了你才能上
It means you go on if one of the leads can't make the performance.
我不喜欢冒犯你 小妹 但你也是个替补
Well I hate to break it to you sister but you're one too.
不同的是我会唱歌
The difference being I can carry a tune.
听着 我不会和你唱歌 除非头发着火
Listen babe. I wouldn't sing with you if my hair was on fire
而你正好是世界上最后一桶水
and you were the last bucket of water on earth.
我也不会和你唱歌 除非我快饿死
I wouldn't sing with you if I were starving
而你是唯一的一罐泡菜
and you were the last pickle at the picnic.
什么时候一起吃顿饭
Want to go to lunch sometime
先生们 发动引擎吧
Gentlemen start your engines.
这也是我想说的 哥们
That's what I'm talking about bro.
-来看看这些吉他 -好的
-yo come check out these guitars. -Yeah.
这是什么
What is this
"斯坦福荣誉学位项目诚挚的..."
"Stanford's honors program cordially..."
天啊
Oh my gosh.
Oh my goodness!
"你和29位学生被邀请参与荣誉课程"
"You and 29 students are invited for early orientation."
天啊 天大的消息 你妈妈一定会很自豪
Oh my gosh that's huge. Your mom must be so proud.
泰勒 只有你一个人知道
Taylor you're the only one that knows.
你已经接受了 对吧
But you've already accepted right
我要为你办个离别晚会 这太重要了
I'm throwing a going-away party. This is huge!
你别想这么容易就把我打发了
You can't get rid of me that easy.
别忘了我们还要做年鉴呢
We've got a yearbook to do. Remember
-回去工作 -好的
-Back to work. -OK.
这些是夏培的年鉴照片
These are Sharpay's yearbook photos.
没错 谢谢
Of course they are. Thank you.
-最好是好消息 -他们只招30个新生
-This'd better be good. -They select only 30 freshmen
从全部新生里面精挑细选
From the entire incoming class.
这是三周的荣誉课程
It's a special three-week honor program.
真是难得的机会
How prestigious.
但是这项活动两周后就要开始了
But the program starts in two weeks.
她将错过我们的...不 是你的表演
She'd miss our sh...your show.
天啊 这该怎么办
Oh my goodness. What to do
这次演出可耽误不得 不是吗
The show must go on mustn't it
-早上好 -早上好
-Morning. -Morning.
只想和你在一起
我有太多的事要做
I got a lot of things I have to do
让我心烦意乱
All these distractions
未来已摆在我们眼前
Our future's coming soon
我们将要分别
We're being pulled
各分东西
A hundred different directions
但是无论怎样
But whatever happens
我知道你在我身旁...
I know I've got you...
-太美了 -谢谢
-It's beautiful. -Thanks.
我是说真的
I mean really.
这次演出 这次舞会 所有的一切
This the prom number everything.
这次演出一定会大获成功
It's going to be a great show.
说到舞会 你还在这干什么
Speaking of prom what are you doing
还有两天就要公演了
It's two days before the show.
我在写管弦乐还有编曲
I'm writing orchestrations and fixing charts.
我还要写歌词
I still have to write lyrics.
好极了 我8点来接你
Great. I'll pick you up at 8:00.
我的思绪中满是你的影子
You're on my mind you're in my heart
无论我们身在何方
It doesn't matter where we are
此情永不移
We'll be all right
即使我们相隔千里
Even if we're miles apart
我只想
All I wanna do
和你在一起
Is be with you
Be with you
克服一切困难
There's nothing we can't do
只想和你在一起
Just wanna be with you only you
不论人生中的起起伏伏
No matter where life takes us
-我们永不分离 -这话千真万确
-Nothing can break us apart -You know it's true
我只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you
-太棒了 -好极了
-Great! -Awesome.
和你在一起
Just be with you
人生总是充满变幻
You know how life can be it changes overnight
晴天也会转阴 但这都无所谓
It's sunny then raining but it's all right
-有你这样的朋友 -总能帮我排忧解难
-A friend like you -Always makes it easy
-你永远陪伴我 -一直都是
-I know that you get me -Every time
无论是起是伏
Through every up through every down
我都会伴你左右
you know I'll always be around
任何时候你都可以依靠我
Through anything you can count on me
我只想
All I wanna do
和你在一起
Is be with you
Be with you
克服一切困难
There's nothing we can't do
只想和你在一起
Just wanna be with you only you
无论人生是起是伏
No matter where life takes us
我们永不分离
Nothing can break us apart
这是我们永恒的誓言
You know it's true
只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you
太棒了 彩排很成功
Bravo! Great rehearsal.
可惜你的搭档得跟着你的拍子走
Pity the actor that has to follow you.
你是说你自己吧 舞蹈指导
I believe that actor is you Mr. Choreographer.
是吗
Oh really
-好了 休息五分钟 然后再来一遍 -好的
-Ok let's take five and run it again. -Yes!
-瑞恩 -大家听好了 就五分钟
-Ryan! -That's five everybody.
你从凯尔西那搞到那首歌了吗
Did you get a copy of that song from Kelsi
没有 但我邀请了她去舞会
No. but I'm taking her to prom.
干得好 与朋友保持亲密 同敌人要更亲密
Brilliant. Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
给我把那个二重奏搞到手
Now get me that duet.
那个...夏培 你和盖比瑞拉不一样
Uh...Sharpay you are not Gabriella.
不要枉下结论
Don't be so sure.
-波比 -那两个孩子又来了
-Hey Bobby. -Hey the boys are back.
-你好 鲍勃 -最近好吗
-Hey Bob. -How are you
-瑞雷先生 -特洛伊
-Mr. Riley. -Troy.
你的引擎听起来不太正常
There is nothing like the purr of a well-tuned engine.
绝对出毛病了
That wasn't it.
我的燃油泵挂掉了
Yeah. My fuel pump's deceased.
你能给我安个散热器加水盖吗
You have a radiator cap for me
-听说过大力胶吗 -我现在用的就是这个
-Heard of duct tape -That's what I got on it now.
随你们翻 我保证能找到你们想要的
Dig around over there. I'm sure you'll find what you want.
我简直太兴奋了
I am so excited about
你们下学期要加入阿尔伯克基大学球队
You boys playing at the U of A next year.
我可已经买了季票了 今天我得早点走
I bought my season tickets. I got to take off early today
你们搞定后把门给我锁好
So lock up when you're done.
-没问题 -你们知道钥匙放在哪
-Yeah. -You know where the key is.
-帮我和你们教练问声好 -好的
-Say "hey" to coach. -Will do.
你听到没 他说他买了季票
Did you hear that He's got season tickets.
我们也该加把劲练习了
Time to start practicing.
放松 勒布朗
Take a breather LeBron.
你不觉得我们的未来已经被规划好了吗
Feel like your future is laid out in front of you
-你想说什么 -我也不知道
-What is your point -I don't know.
我只想创造自己的未来
I just want my future to be my future.
你有注意过自己的表演吗
Do you see what happens when you do a show
你就像 就像一人分饰五角
You're like five people.
那又怎样 这不好吗
Yeah but what's so bad about that
小时候来这玩的时候 我们能扮演十个人
We used to come here as kids we'd be ten people.
像是间谍 超级英雄 摇滚明星
We'd be spies superheroes rock stars.
拿着这个
Hold this.
只要我们愿意
We were whatever we wanted to be
我们可以在任何时候扮演任何人
Whenever we wanted to be it.
我们当时就是这个样子
It was us.
没错 那是什么时候来着 8岁吧
Yeah we were like eight years old.
从纪录来看 我扮演的超级英雄比你强多了
For the record I was a better superhero than you were.
回想当初
Take it back to the place when you know it all began
我们可以随意扮演任何角色
We could be anything we wanna be
喧嚣声中 当年的那群孩子又回来了
We can tell by the noise that the boys are back again
一起来刷新历史
Together making history
是时候展示
It's time to show how
如何成为超级英雄
To be a superhero
就像与
Just like a showdown
威尔·史密斯还有劳勃·狄尼洛挑战
Will smith and Bobby De Niro
毋庸置疑我们是最棒的
We're the best no doubt
和以前一样
Doing it like we used to do
这是我们的地盘
This is our town yeah
我要告诉你们的是
And I'm telling you
我们又回来了
Oh the boys are back hey the boys are back
没错
That's right
我们又回来了 和以前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
把邻居们都吵醒
Gonna wake up the neighborhood
我们又回来了 我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back all right
随心所欲的爬墙
Climbing up the walls any time we want
不必啰嗦 我们又回到了从前
The word is out the boys are back
我们又回来了
The boys are back
回来挽救世界
Back to save the day
我们又回来了
The boys are back
紧握正义 战无不胜
Keep coming with the right win the fight every single time
在我们的地盘 我们不可战胜
Undefeated here in our house yeah
无论何时只要愿意 我们就能成为摇滚明星
We can rock we can shock any time we like
今晚我们要玩个痛快
And tonight we're going all out
是时候展示
It's time to show how
如何成为超级英雄
To be a superhero oh
就像一次挑战
Just like a showdown
加足马力 全速前进
Keep the pedal to the metal go!
毋庸置疑我们是最棒的
We're the best no doubt
还是和以前一样
Doing it like we used to do
这是我们的地盘
This is our town
告诉你们 快看
And I'm telling you oh look out
我们又回来了
The boys are back hey
-我们又回来了 -没错
-The boys are back -That's right
我们又回来了 和以前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
把邻居们吵醒
Gonna wake up the neighborhood
我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah
The boys are back
随心所欲的爬墙 不要啰嗦
Climbing up the walls any time we want the word is out
我们又回来了
The boys are back
回来改变世界
Here to change the world
揭开谜团 挺身而战
To solve the mystery fight the battle
拯救自己心爱的女孩
Save the girl
我们势不可挡
No one no one can stop us now
规则由我们掌控
We're the ones that make the rules
我们又回来了
The boys are back
The boys are back hey the boys are back that's right
我们又回来了 和以前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
把邻居们吵醒
Gonna wake up the neighborhood
我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back all right
随心所欲的爬墙
Climbing up the walls any time we want
毋庸担心 因为...
No need to worry 'cause...
我们又回来了
The boys are back hey the boys are back
我们又回来了 和从前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
我们让一切变得更好
And we make it look good
我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back
随意粉碎阻挡我们的高墙
Tearing down the walls any time we want
我想你们现在该明白了
I'm sure that you know by now
我们又回来了
The boys are back
如果被茱莉亚音乐学院录取了 有什么打算
What are you gonna do if Juilliard says yes
-我不知道 -我最讨厌听你这么说
-I don't know. -That's not what I wanted to hear.
给我听好 明天球场上我一定让你清醒清醒
I'm getting your butt back in the gym tomorrow. Got me
那样我就能轻易打你个稀巴烂了
So I can whup your butt
别做梦了 除非我挂了
Dream on. With my eyes closed.
你该庆祝庆祝的 别保密
You should be celebrating.no keeping it secret
问题是下周就开始了 我会错过的
The problem is it's start next week. I'll miss everything
不会的 只是表演
No, you won't. Just the show.
你可以在毕业舞会时回来
You can come back for prom and graduation.
你未来一片光明 你得把握机会
Your future is loud and clear you have to grab what you can
泰勒 你别像我妈妈一样
Tyler, would you stop to be mother for
只做我的朋友吧
A second and just to be my friend
我或许会喜欢这里 或许想留下来 多久都没问题
You know, maybe I like it here. Maybe I want to stay as long as possible
或许明年我就待在这里
Maybe I just stay here next year
什么
What
就在阿尔伯克基吗 那没有意义
Stay in Albuquerque That makes no sense.
我为什么要做有意义的事情
And why do I have to make such things sense
一年后我会去斯坦福大学的
I still go to Stanford and just maybe in a year.
明年秋天我还会在阿尔伯克基大学上课
You know I can take classes in U of A next fall
你是说阿尔伯克基大学
Do you say you U of A
显然你太过草率
It's obviously you do not think clearly
因为你在考虑特洛伊
Because you are thinking about Troy.
我理解 但是第一次心动...而且...
I mean I got it, but you first crush...but...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我是说 初恋
I meant relationship.
还会有别的男孩让你倾心的
But there would be other guys, I promise.
嗯 我...我...我要误晚饭了
Emm, I'm...I'm...I'm late for dinner.
高中就好像
You know, high school feels like the most
人生中最重要的阶段
Important things in the world you've been in it
它会改变我们
But that change us
不是一切都得改变的 妈妈
Not everything has changed. Mom
我不相信
I don't believe that.
这是曾经也幻想给天上的
And this is from the girl who used to think she could just
星星充电的女孩给你的建议
recharping, rechanging the stars in the sky.
世事难料 亲爱的
Sometimes it just happens, sweetheart.
不论我们的意志如何
When we want to or not.
我爱你(西班牙语)
I love you.
我也爱你 妈妈
I love you too. Mom.
第一场比赛这里进行 下一场比赛对阵绵羊
Hey first game is here, but next game is away against to lame
是新爱尔兰队 是吗
Oh that's New Ireland, right.
-敬我的孩子 -敬我的孩子
-to my boy. -to my boy.
红鹰队
Red hawks.
如果此情能永留
If this would forever
在我们见证前永久
or it could be better before we proved it was
但两千一百二十三小时的阻隔
but two thousand one hundred's twenty three hours.
让大地闭合
abending the universe
永远不变
it's gonna make it breath
在我们家中复苏
in our home without changing
永远不变
without changing
我们在何方
and do you know where we are
我们在哪里
where we are
都会与众不同
we're never be the same
此时
Right here
此刻
Right now
-此刻 -更待何时只有...
-Right now. -You can wait for some other day to be...
只有...但此时只有你和我
to be...but right now it's you and me
你和我
you and me
-你和我 -但此时只有...
-Oh, you and me. -but right now it's...
你和我
you and me
你好 特洛伊
Hi Troy!
我还没向你祝贺呢
I realized I haven't offered my congratulations.
谢谢 真高兴这赛季终于结束了...
Oh thank you. I'm glad the season's over so...
我不是说篮球 傻小子 我是说盖比瑞拉
I didn't mean basketball silly! I meant Gabriella.
-什么 -她没法和我们一起演出了
-What -Her missing the show
多少让人有些失望
Is a little disappointing
但是能参加斯坦福的荣誉课程
But being selected for Stanford's honors program
对她和东高都太棒了
That is amazing for her and for East High.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
别人都知道 整个学校都在沸沸扬扬的讨论
Everyone else does. The whole school's buzzing.
荣誉人将有机会接触斯坦福最优秀的教授
The honorees spend time with Stanford's top professors
从下星期开始
Starting next week.
-下周 -看 这里写着呢
-Next week? -Look right there.
你真的不知道吗
You really didn't know?
这是有点尴尬
Ok this is a little awkward.
我猜她不告诉你
I guess her not telling you means that
因为她还没做出决定
She's on the fence about it.
但是比起特洛伊·波顿还有谁更有资格
But who better than Troy Bolton
去鼓励她接受这项荣誉呢
To encourage her to accept the honor
况且让她拿不定主意的
Since the only thing possibly holding her back
可能就是...你
Would be...you.
好了 彩排时见啦 回见
Well I'll see you at rehearsal. Toodles.
你好
Hello
你好 有人订了一个匹萨吗
Hello. Somebody order a pizza pie
-我可没有订 -这是特别奉送
-I didn't order a pizza. -Special delivery!
玛格丽特匹萨
Margherita pizza!
都是你喜欢的
Just the way you like it.
不要忘了
Let's not forget
少了巧克力草莓 野餐会是什么样子
What's a picnic without chocolate-covered strawberries
一定糟透了
It wouldn't be right.
你想吃最后一个草莓吗
Do you want the last strawberry
吃吧 这可能恰好是
Come on. This might very well be
世界上最好的草莓
The best strawberry in the whole world
你不吃就不知道它有多美味
You wouldn't know because you're not gonna eat it.
好吧
Fine then.
被你说对了
You were right.
有件事想问你
So here's the thing.
关于你的斯坦福荣誉课程...
Your honors program at Stanford...
你怎么知道的
How did you hear about that
很多人都知道了
A lot of people heard about it.
但你却没通知我 为什么
But I wasn't one of them. Why
因为我知道你会说什么
Because I knew what you would say.
毫无疑问你应该参加这次荣誉课程
Of course you should do the honors program.
这就是你上次想要和我说的吗
Is that what you were trying to tell me
那天在后院里
In the backyard the other day
这是其中一件
One of the things.
还有什么
What else
我在考虑说服我妈让我留下来
I've been thinking about trying to talk my mom into staying
在阿尔伯克基再待一年
In Albuquerque another year.
就在这先参加些课程
I'll just take some classes here
等我准备好了 就去斯坦福
And go to Stanford when I'm ready.
你不能放弃斯坦福 这千载难逢
You can't just put off something as amazing as Stanford.
你应该去 这才是正确的选择
You got to go. It's the right thing.
我一直都在做正确的选择
I always do the right thing.
或许这次我想疯狂点
Maybe I want to be a little crazy this time.
我的人生一直都是在全速前进
Everything about my life has always been full speed ahead.
我和你说过 我想慢慢来...
I told you I wish it would all just slow down...
暂时停一停
To a stop.
我们马上就要毕业了
We're going to graduate.
这些没法改变 也没法慢慢来
That's going to happen. Nothing is going to slow down.
或许我的心已不在高中了
I guess my heart just doesn't know it's in high school.
特洛伊 你什么都不需要说
Troy,you don't have to say anything else.
我比你更擅长道别
I'm a lot better at goodbyes than you.
我可是下过苦功做过练习的
I've had a ton of practice.
为什么要现在说再见
Why are you saying goodbye
我们还要参加舞会呢 我们还没毕业
We still have prom. We still have to graduate.
我是说"晚安"
I meant "good night."
-你还好吧 -嗯
-You ok -Yeah.
-晚安 -晚安
-Good night. -Good night.
我想我本该更清楚
I guess I should've known better
幸运女神已不再垂青我
To believe that my luck had changed
我付出我的灵魂
Oh I let my heart and forever
最终彼此相识
Finally learn each other's name
告诉自己这次会不同
I tell myself this time it's different
不说再见 因为说不出口
No goodbyes 'cause I can't bear to say it
如果留下来
I'd never survive the one that's coming
我无法面对即将到来的离别
If I stay oh no
就这样离开 不要回首
Just walk away and don't look back
因为如果心碎了 将会倍受折磨
'Cause if my heart breaks it's gonna hurt so bad
你知道我很坚强 但这次我却无法忍受
You know I'm strong but I can't take that
趁着还来得及
Before it's too late
就这样离开
Oh just walk away
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Oh just walk away
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Oh just walk away
我知道是时候该放手
I've got to let it go
来保护我的灵魂我的心
Start protecting my heart and soul
因为我已无法再一次面对离别
'Cause I don't think I'll survive a goodbye again
无法再次面对
Not again
就这样离开 不要回首
Just walk away oh and don't look back
因为如果心碎了 将会倍受折磨
'Cause if my heart breaks it's gonna hurt so bad
你知道我很坚强 但这次我却无法忍受
You know I'm strong but I can't take that
趁着还来得及
Before it's too late
就这样离开
Just walk away
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Walk away walk away yeah
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Walk away walk away
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Walk away walk away
Walk walk walk away
就这样离开
Walk away walk away
好了 大家 都注意了 听好了
All right everyone! Attention please! Listen up.
你们当中可能有人已经知道了
As some of you know
蒙特兹不能继续参加我们的演出了
Miss Montez is no longer available to us.
但是 演出还是得继续下去
However the show must indeed go on.
夏培 你接替盖比瑞拉 和特洛伊唱二重唱
So Sharpay you will do Gabriella's duet with Troy.
缇安拉 做好准备接替夏培了吗
Tiara ready to step in for Sharpay
我可穿不进她那些亮闪闪的鞋
Those sparkling shoes are impossible to fill.
别担心 凯尔西会帮你的
Don't worry. Kelsi will work with you.
拜托 大家都振作起来
Come on people. Let's rise to the occasion.
我们都是专业人士
We're all pros here.
就当为了盖比瑞拉 好吧
Let's do it for Gabriella. Ok
凯尔西 特洛伊 瑞恩伴奏
Kelsi Troy Ryan play piano.
好了 我们还有一堆工作要做呢
All right we have a lot of work to do.
我们得漆背景 排练第二幕 开始吧
There are sets to paint. Drill that second number. Let's go!
都给我快点 快点
Come on people double time!
-很晚了 -是啊
-It's late. -Yeah.
和盖比瑞拉联系了吗
Hear from Gabriella
嗯
Yeah.
她正和斯坦福的天才们打得火热
She's knee-deep in geniuses out there.
信不信由你 她说那的吃的比东高好
Believe it or not she says the food's better at East High.
是吗
Yeah. Oh yeah.
她还会参加舞会吗
She still coming down for prom
嗯
Yeah.
演出准备的怎么样了
How's that big show going
你不会感兴趣的
You don't want to know.
你打算什么时候告诉我这个
When were you going to tell me about this
茱莉亚音乐学院
Juilliard.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
或许你有想说的
Well maybe there is.
听说你相中别的大学了
I heard you're talking to other schools.
没搞错吧
I mean is this serious
不单阿尔伯克基大学相中我了 老爸
U of A isn't the only school that's talked to me dad.
你又不是不知道
You know that.
我只和你谈阿尔伯特大学
But it's the only school we talked about.
你若改变主意
Chad would be approximately disappointed
查德会失望的
If you decided to change your mind.
不 查德会缓过来的
No Chad would get over it.
你会吗
Would you?
儿子 从小到大
Son we've been going to U of A games
我一直带你去看阿尔伯克基大学篮球赛
Ever since you were a little kid.
你唯一渴望的
All you ever talked about
就是进校队 披上红鹰战袍
Was wearing that Red hawk's uniform.
我不是孩子了 爸
But I'm not a little kid anymore dad.
您养我 是为我能自己做出选择
You raise me to make my own choices
我需要自强自立
And I need to make them.
而不是任您 查德或他人左右 由我自己选
Not you or Chad or anybody else. Me.
特洛伊 别这样 特洛伊
Troy come on. Troy!
那天 当门轻轻关上
The day a door is closed
回音久久绕心间
The echoes fill your soul
看不清前进方向
They won't say which way to go
只好由心把路照亮
Just trust your heart
努力追寻心中梦想
To find what you're here for
开启另一扇窗
Open another door
左思右想
But I'm not sure anymore
原来一切已太难
It's just so hard
杂音充斥耳边
Voices in my head
对我左指右点
Tell me they know best
将我推向无底深渊
Got me on the edge
推啊 推啊 推啊
They're pushing pushing they're pushing
他们虽有雕虫小技
I know they've got a plan
命运握我自己手里
But the ball's in my hands
今次大战一对一
This time it's man to man
我奔驰漂移 奋战到底
I'm driving fighting inside
在颠覆的世界
A world that's upside down
在急转的世界
And spinning faster
没你我该怎么办
What do I do now without you
何去何从
I don't know where to go
举棋不定
What's the right team
我要一片天
I want my own thing
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm going to scream
无从选择
I can't choose
心乱神伤
So confused
奈何奈何
What's it all mean
我有一个梦
I want my own dream
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm going to scream
架起无影脚
I'm kicking down the walls
砖墙尽踢倒
I've gotta make them fall
铁壁和铜墙
Just break through them all
穿透并毁掉
I'm punching crashing
追寻现实真我
I'm gonna fight to find myself
决心将纠缠摆脱
Me and no one else
哪边 谁告诉我
Which way I can't tell
摸索 摸索
I'm searching searching
不知往哪转弯的我
Can't find the way that I should turn
向左走 还是向右走
I should turn right or left
没有你 无法选择 无法记得
It's like nothing works without you
何去何从
I don't know where to go
举棋不定
What's the right team
我要一片天
I want my own thing
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm gonna scream
无从选择
I can't choose
心乱神伤
So confused
奈何奈何
What's it all mean
我有一个梦
I want my own dream
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm gonna scream
光阴似箭 光阴似水
Yeah the clock's running down
喧闹人群
Hear the crowd getting loud
侧耳倾听 消损殆尽
I'm consumed by the sound
难道是她 难道是爱
Is it her is it love
音乐之声 尽情唱响
Can the music ever be enough
来吧 来吧
Gotta work it out
你能行 你能行
You can do it
何去何从
I don't know where to go
举棋不定
What's the right team
我要一片天
I want my own thing
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm gonna scream
无从选择
I can't choose
心乱神伤
So confused
奈何奈何
What's it all mean
我有一个梦
I want my own dream
如此强烈 放声呐喊
So bad I'm gonna scream
达老师
Miss D
我知道我不该在这儿
I know I'm not supposed to be here.
是吗
Aren't you
我也本不该这会儿来这的
Well nor should I be at this hour I suppose
只因蒙特兹缺席而让夏培代演
But I am trying to rebalance a show
我想来这找些灵感 确保演出万无一失
In which Sharpay now plays the role of Miss Montez.
你来这做什么
And the reason for your visit is
不知道 只是觉得这地方能让我...
I don't know. I think I feel like this is a good place to...
-尖叫 感受自由 -或能沉思片刻吧
-Scream feel free. -Or just to think.
自我发现过程中
The stage can be a wonderful partner
舞台是不错的搭档
In the process of self-discovery.
舞台上 你很放得开
You seem comfortable up there.
真的吗
I do
那就是为何我会以你名义
Which is why I submitted an application
向茱莉亚音乐学院提交申请
In your name to Juilliard.
原来是您啊
It was you.
十年前 或许有许多选择已擦肩而过
Better to consider opportunities now
而今 好好把握 机遇可遇不可求
Than in ten years when life may limit your choices.
如果做得过分了 我道歉
If I overstepped I apologize.
没有 我并没生气
No. no I'm not mad.
只是有点迷惘
I'm just confused.
演艺生涯让我体会到
What a life in the theater has taught me is
要相信人的直觉
To trust one's instincts.
那是需要勇气的
And that takes courage.
你完全具备这种品质
A quality you don't seem to lack.
谁最后走谁关灯
Last one out turns off the lights.
往前几步 跳进来
So walk walk walk. Jump in.
携手画个圈 再转出去
Around the world and spin out.
懂么 学会了吧
See You got it.
-比起她 还是和你跳来的容易 -该我了
-You're easier to dance with than she is. -Okay my turn.
好的 重头再来一遍
Ok. Here we go. From the top.
往前几步 跳进来 携手画个圈
Walk walk walk. Jump down. Around the world.
小心 小心
Heads up! Heads up!
好 大家休息5分钟好吧 休息5分钟
All right everyone. Let's just take five all right Take five.
你俩 把房子扶起来
You two. House up.
篮球少年 过来
Hoops man. Over here.
看来你过得很愉快
You look like you're having the time of your life.
我把舞搞砸了 把所有歌也搞砸了
I'm messing up the dances. I'm messing up all the songs.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们都有责任 原因大家都很清楚
It's all of us. And all of us pretty much know why.
如果没有盖比瑞拉
If it wasn't for Gabriella
这场演出又成"夏培秀"了
This musical would have been another "Sharpay Show."
-会好的 -是啊
-It'll be fine. -Yeah.
-嗨 妈妈 -好啊
-Hey mama! -Hi.
太帅了
Gorgeous!
我不知哪件好 盖比瑞拉帮选了这件 所以...
Yeah I'd like to take credit but Gabriella picked it out. So...
你相中的胸花 我帮你订了
Oh I ordered that corsage that you showed me.
两者搭配 天衣无缝
It's going to be perfect.
谢谢老妈
Oh thanks mom.
-你干得很棒 -谢谢
-Oh you did good. -Thank you.
盖比瑞拉打来的
Hey it's Gabriella.
我刚给老妈看了你挑的晚礼服
Hey! I just showed my mom the tux.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我现在还不能像个大人一样 特洛伊
I can't be a little adult right now Troy.
希望你能理解
I'm hoping you understand that.
不 别这么说
No don't even say that.
盖比瑞拉 毕业舞会只有两天了
Gabriella prom is in two days.
现在你本该在飞机上了
You're supposed to be on a plane right now.
我花了两星期 才习惯没你的日子
It's taking me two weeks to get used to being away from you.
-才习惯没有东高和大家的日子 -我知道 我懂
-From East High and all my friends. -I know. I know.
那么我回学校 参加个舞会 又转身离开
So what I come back go to prom and leave again
出席毕业典礼 再转身离开
And then it's graduation and leave again
-我们之前就这么说好的啊 -我想我做不到 特洛伊
-That was our plan. -I don't think I can do it Troy.
我恐怕连再见都说不出口了
I think I've run out of goodbyes.
为什么你一直说再见呢
Why do you keep saying goodbye
我爱你 小野猫
I love you wildcat.
可我得呆这儿 对不起
But I need to stay right where I am. I'm sorry.
盖比瑞拉
Gabriella.
她不打算回来了 兄弟
She's not coming back man.
-她错过舞会了 -不 她再也不回来了
-Is she going to miss prom -No she's not coming back at all.
太糟了 兄弟
Wow. That's lousy man.
糟透了
It really is.
但是 兄弟
But hey man.
人人都知道 高中后
Everybody knows you don't bring the girl
你又恢复单身了
With you after high school.
和往常一样 盖比瑞拉已先你一步了
Look Gabriella is already one step ahead. As usual.
现在该你振作了 兄弟
Right now you got to snap out of it dude.
她已经去斯坦福大学了
She's off to Stanford.
听着 我会陪你的
Hey and look I am right there with you.
泰勒会考上耶鲁大学
Taylor's heading to Yale.
你和我到时一起上阿尔伯克基大学
And you and I are going to U of A.
球赛新篇章又将开启
It's a whole new ball game.
也许篮球已不再是我生命的全部了 兄弟
Maybe I don't see my life as a ball game anymore man.
听着
Look.
你可以和我们一起去舞会
You're gonna go to the prom with us
我们都是你的朋友
You're gonna be with all your friends.
你会玩尽兴的 是吧
You're gonna have a good time. All right
我可没想过要错过舞会
Well I don't plan on missing my prom.
这就对了
There we go.
我就知道 你最后一个离开教学楼
I figured you'd be the last one out of the building.
我不是在做梦吧
I don't believe this.
在去舞会的路上 我拐错道了
I took a wrong turn on the way to prom.
你也是
So did you.
你太疯狂了 小野猫
You are so crazy wildcat.
你爬到树上做什么
And what is it with you and trees
我猜 站树上看得更清楚些
I guess I see things more clearly from up here.
你看起来很帅
Well you look handsome.
舞会今晚在阿尔伯克基举行 离这儿一千公里远
Prom is tonight in Albuquerque. A thousand miles away.
我的舞会 与你相随
My prom is wherever you are.
若我要在东部高中与谁共舞
If I'm gonna have a last dance at East High
那非你莫属
It's gonna be with you.
握我的手 领你开始跳舞
Take my hand I'll take the lead
每次旋转 我都细心呵护
And every turn will be safe with me
不必害怕 害怕摔跤失足
Don't be afraid afraid to fall
你的倩影 我会牢牢抱住
You know I'll catch you through it all
-无法拆散我们 -即使海角天涯
-And you can't keep us apart -Even a thousand miles
无法拆散我们
Can't keep us apart
因为我心与你相随
'Cause my heart is wherever you are
寻寻觅觅
It's like catching lightning
与你相遇
The chances of finding
甚是不易
someone like you
万里挑一
It's one in a million
你我恋情
The chances of feeling
相连一起
the way we do
我们舞步轻盈
And with every step together
我们携手共进
We just keep on getting better
-能否共舞一曲 -能否共舞一曲
-So can I have this dance -Can I have this dance
能否共舞一曲
Can I have this dance
-能否共舞一曲 -共舞一曲
-Can I have this dance -This dance
能否共舞一曲
Can I have this dance
知道吗...
You know...
你转学到东部高中后 不单我变了
I'm not the only one that changed when you came to East High.
曾和我擦肩而过的小子们...我们变朋友了
Kids that I used to just pass in the hallway...we're friends now.
我们本该今晚一起同台演出的
And we're supposed to be doing a show together.
问题是 东部高中曾因你到来而变
The problem is East High changed when you got there.
如今 也因你离去而变
And now it's changed again because you left.
也许 你已准备好向东部高中挥手道别
You might be ready to say goodbye to East High
可东部高中还没准备好
But East High's not ready to say goodbye to you.
女士们先生们 节目快要开始了
Ladies and gentlemen this is the final call for curtain.
请速入座
Find your seats.
老爸老妈 非洲之行如何 不 我是说印度
Hey mommy and daddy how was Africa No I mean India.
好极了 那个 演出就要开始了
Oh fabulous. Ok well the show is starting soon.
你们在剧厅了
Oh you're in the lobby
好的 回头见 我爱死你们送的玫瑰了
Ok. Toodles. And I love the roses!
你好吗 虽没和你正式见过面
Hey what's up We haven't formally met
可我却有种似曾相识的感觉
But I feel like I know you in sort of a vibe level.
我是"火箭人"吉米·萨拉
I'm Jimmy "the rocket" Zara.
"火箭人"吉米 什么玩意
Jimmy "the rocket" What are you
像木偶黑帮之类的东西
Something like a Muppet gangster
什么味儿 是你的古龙水还是毒气外泄
Oh. What is that Is that your cologne or a toxic spill
这个啊"黯然销魂水"专为演出买的
Oh yeah. It's called "Babe Magnet." bought it just for the show.
你喜欢吗
You like it
呃 太恶心了
Eww! That is so gross.
喂 让特洛伊来见我 得和他试唱一下
Hello! Send Troy in to see me. I need to run the song.
狄昂 特洛伊·波顿给我发了条短信
Yo! Dion. Troy Bolton just sent me a text.
可能正在入场
Probably just checking in.
"开了整晚的车 我争取赶上第二幕"
"Been driving all night. I'll try to make it for the second act."
-"祝好运" -"祝好运" 什么意思
-"Break a leg." -"Break a leg" What does that mean
哥们 今晚演出"由你撑排场"
Dude that's show biz for "you're going on tonight."
-代替特洛伊 -没错
-As Troy -Yeah.
-在台上演出 -没错
-Onstage -Yeah.
-不是吧 -击掌庆贺吧
-Oh no. -Get it!
好吧 通知夏培
All right notify Sharpay.
凯尔西和管弦乐队那边我搞定
I will take care of Kelsi and the orchestra.
等下 达老师
Hold up Miss D.
我想他停止呼吸了
I think he stopped breathing.
给他来个海姆利克氏治疗法 好戏上场了
Well then give him the Heimlich! It's show time!
-帮他理理 -来吧
-Go get him. -Come on.
-你好 埃文斯女士 -你好
-Hello Mrs. Evans. -Hello.
-请尽情欣赏 -谢谢
-Enjoy the show. -Thank you.
茱莉亚音乐学院贵宾席
Reserved for Juilliard
-很棒吧 对了 座位在这儿 -谢谢
-So wonderful oh yes. Seats right here. -Thank you.
谢谢你们的到来 请尽情欣赏演出
Thank you for coming. Enjoy the show.
最后一次 把舞台分享
It's our last chance to share the stage
毕业之后 将天各一方
Before we go our separate ways
高中生涯 不能永伴成长
High School wasn't meant to last forever
最后一次 我们发热发光
It's our last chance for us to shine
最后一次 音乐伴你身旁
To bring you music one more time
来吧 来吧 来吧
So come on come on come on
Come on come on come on
来吧 来吧 来吧
W I L D 野猫队 你最牛
W-I-L-D wildcats! You know you're on
W I L D 野猫队 加油 加油
W-I-L-D wildcats! Come on come on
东高帅哥们 来点轰动吧
East High boys let's make some noise
W-I-L-D 野猫队 拉风时间到啦
Oh yeah W-I-L-D wildcats! Now's the time
最后一次 施展球技
This is the last time to get it right
最后一晚 闪耀舞台
This is the last chance to make it our night
我们使出 看家本领
We got to show what we're all about
团队合作 所向披靡
Team work together
最后一场 赢取比分
This is the last chance to make our mark
篮坛史册 铭记我们
History will know who we are
巅峰之战 要打得完美
This is the last game so make it count
机不可失 时不再来...
It's now or never...
进来
Entree.
晚上好埃文斯小姐 2分钟后就该你上场了
Good evening Miss Evans. Two minutes till places.
很好 让特洛伊来这好吗
Oh good. Can you tell Troy to come up here
想和他排练下接吻戏
I want to rehearse the kissing.
难道没人通知你 特洛伊他...
Hasn't anybody told you that Troy...
快去啊
Go!
我全部都要 我都要 都要 都要
I want it all I want it want it want it
我的门上会有属于自己的星
I gotta have my star on the door
我要全世界 什么都不能少
I want the world nothing less
所有名流雅士和报刊 只会给我最好评价
All the glam and the press only giving me the best reviews
我全部想要 我想要 想要 想要
I want it all want it all want it all want it all
他是舞蹈编导
He's the choreographer.
转起来吧 美眉们
Kick it girls
我全部想要 我想要 想要 想要
I want it all want it all want it all
我全部想要 我想要
Want it all want it all
We want it all
谢谢你 我的乐队
My band! Thank you!
东部高中 你太神奇了 晚安
East High you're amazing! Good night.
儿子好样的
That's my boy!
我们得加点东西
We have to save something.
我在阳台时 别忘了特效
I'm at the balcony don't forget the special.
你总忘加特效
You're always forgetting the special ok.
特洛伊在哪 好吧 他一定在某个角落
Where's Troy Ok he's around here somewhere.
裤裤好可爱哦
Oh. Cute pants. Oh.
-该你上场了 -哦了
-You're on. -Oh.
我有太多的事要做
I got a lot of things I have to do
让我心烦意乱 未来已摆在我们眼前
All these distractions our future's coming soon
我们将要分别 各分东西
We're being pulled a hundred different directions
全神贯注 吉米 加油
Focus Jimmy. Come on man.
我的思绪中满是你的影子
You're on my mind you're in my heart
无论我们身在何方
It doesn't matter where we are
此情永不移
We'll be all right
即使我们相隔千里
Even if we're miles apart
即使我们相隔 相隔 相隔千里
Even if we're miles and miles and miles apart
似乎出问题了
I think we have a problem.
我只想
All I wanna do
和你在一起
Is be with you
Be with you
克服一切困难
There's nothing we can't do
-只想和你在一起 -只有你
-Just wanna be with you -Only you
无论身在哪里
And no matter where life takes us
我们永不分离
Nothing can break us apart
-我只想...-呃
-I just wanna be with...-Eww.
和你在一起
You
谢谢
Thank you very much.
-你太牛了 -第一次见这么多人捧场
-You rule! -Best crowd I've ever had.
真棒啊 搞吧 拯救世界吧 大英雄
Oh perfect. Go for it. Save the day. Whoopee!
什么
What
你们过来瞧瞧
You guys got to see this.
不 你们很棒 谢谢
No you guys are awesome. Thank you.
-他们来了 -凯尔西
-They're here! -Kelsi!
-上吧 轮到你们了 -哦 伙计
-Let's go! You're on! -Oh man. Hey!
那可是我的衣服啊
That's my dress!
我做了件一样的 比你的更好
I had one made just like it. Only better.
我替演夏培 记得吗
I'm playing Sharpay remember
你不是歌手 不过是个伦敦女学生
You're not a singer. You're a London schoolgirl.
对 伦敦学院戏剧表演系
Yes. London Academy of Dramatic Arts.
我当你助手只想了解学校规矩
I took the job with you to learn the ropes at East High.
目的已达成
Now I have.
让开点
Now step aside.
我得准备下给人留下好印象
I need to warm up and give a good first impression.
因为明年就轮到我做戏剧社的头了
Since it will be my drama department next year.
但你那么忠心 那么贴心
But you were so loyal. So sweet.
那是演戏 你什么时候也可以试试
That's called acting. You should try it sometime.
再见
Toodles.
人生总是充满变幻
You know how life can be it changes overnight
晴天也会转阴 但这都无所谓
It's sunny then raining but it's all right
有朋友如你
A friend like you
总能帮我排忧解难
Always makes it easy
你永远陪伴我
I know that you get me
一直都是
Every time
无论是起是伏 我都会伴你左右
Through every up through every down you know I'll always be around
任何时候你都可以依靠我
Through anything you can count on me
我只想
All I wanna do
-那是特洛伊·波顿 -和你在一起
-That is Troy Bolton. -Is be with you
和你在一起
Be with you
克服一切困难
There's nothing we can't do
只想和你在一起
Just wanna be with you only you
不论人生中的起起伏伏
No matter where life takes us
我们永不分离
Nothing can break us apart
这话千真万确 我只想和你在一起
You know it's true I just wanna be with you
在一起
You
我只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you
有你的日子都是晴天
The sun will always shine
永远阳光普照
That's how you make me feel
此情永不移
We're gonna be all right
因为真爱无敌
'Cause what we have is real
我们会永远相随
And we will always be together
我只想
All I wanna do
和你在一起
Is be with you
Be with you
克服一切困难
There's nothing we can't do
我只想和你在一起
Just wanna be with you only you
无论人生是起是伏
No matter where life takes us
我们永不分离
Nothing can break us apart
这是我们永恒的誓言
You know it's true
只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you
只想
All I wanna do
只想和你在一起
All that I wanna do is be with you
我只想和你在一起
只想和你在一起
All that I wanna do is be with you
All that I wanna do
只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you
夏培·埃文斯 我想你穿错礼服了
Sharpay Evans I believe you're in the wrong costume.
那女孩是谁 如此美丽
Who's that girl She's so fine
那女孩是谁 我不认识
Who's that girl I don't recognize
那女孩是谁 如此漂亮
Who's that girl She looks so good yeah
曾经被你忽视 现在请注意
Guess you never really noticed but you probably should
狂欢吧 在这样一个夜晚
Big fun on the night of nights
今天这样一个夜晚
The night of night's tonight
一起跳舞 就在这个夜晚
Let's dance on the night of nights
我们一定会成功
You know we're gonna do it right
-这将是一个 -你知道
-It's gonna be our night -You know it
-令人难忘的夜晚 -永远记得
-To remember -For all time
-惊喜吧 -狂欢吧
-Surprise. -Big fun
-这将是一个 -我们爱今晚
-It's gonna be the night -We love it
-永不消逝的夜晚 -终生铭记
-To last forever -The rest of our lives
我们永生难忘 今夜将是...
We'll never ever ever forget it's gonna be...
-我的夜晚 -对
-My night -Oh yeah
-在一起 -大声唱起来
-All together -Say it loud
来吧 一起狂欢
Come on now everyone that's right
-这将是一个 -可以肯定
-It's gonna be a night -You can bet
-令人难忘的夜晚 -倾听人群的欢呼吧
-To remember -Hear the crowd
永远永远永远
And never ever ever never ever ever
永永远远不会忘记
Never ever never ever ever forget
-非常感谢 -真是精彩的演出
-Thank you so much. -It was such a great show.
送他们出门 谢谢
See them out please. Thank you.
一起 在一起 每个人
Together together together everyone
在一起 让我们狂欢
Together together come on let's have some fun
女士们先生们 有请我们的毕业生们
Ladies and gentlemen! Our seniors!
凯尔西·尼尔森 茱莉亚学院奖学金获得者
Kelsi Nielsen the Juilliard school scholarship recipient.
音乐
Music.
杰森·克劳斯
Jason Cross.
你成功毕业了
You did it. You graduated.
泰勒·麦肯锡 耶鲁大学 政治科学 荣誉学生
Taylor Mckessie Yale University with honors political science.
我很高兴地宣布
And I am pleased to announce that due
由于今晚的精彩演出
To the excellence displayed here this evening
茱莉亚学院做出了个特别的决定
The Juilliard School has made an extraordinary decision.
额外提供一个奖学金名额
Another senior is being offered a Juilliard scholarship.
恭喜 瑞恩·埃文斯先生 舞蹈艺术专业
Congratulations Mr. Ryan Evans choreography.
另外恭喜 夏培·埃文斯小姐
And congratulations Miss Sharpay Evans.
阿尔伯克基大学 表演艺术专业
University of Albuquerque performing arts.
埃文斯小姐同意今年秋天回到本校
Miss Evans has agreed to return to East High next fall
协助我管理戏剧社
To assist me in running the drama department.
现在有一个毕业生需要做出决定
And now a senior who I believe has a decision to make.
特洛伊·波顿先生 特洛伊
Mr. Troy Bolton. Troy.
我选择篮球
I've chosen basketball.
也选择剧场
But I've also chosen theater.
加州大学伯克利学院提供了我双学位
The University of California Berkeley offers me both.
我下个学期就会去那里
That's where I'm going to be attending next fall.
但最重要是我选择了我心灵的伴侣
But most of all I choose the person who inspires my heart.
因为她我选择了离她32.7英里...
Which is why I picked a school that's exactly 32.7...
...的学校
...miles from you.
盖比瑞拉·蒙特兹小姐 斯坦福大学 法律预科生
Miss Gabriella Montez Stanford University pre-law.
下一位 有请查德·丹弗斯先生
Next Mr. Chad Danforth.
阿尔伯克基大学 篮球专业全奖
University of Albuquerque basketball scholarship!
他不在这里
He's gone.
丹弗斯先生
Mr. Danforth.
他投篮 进了
He goes up for the shot and it's good!
东高野猫队胜利载入史册
East High Wildcat victory for the record books!
他们要颁发毕业证 我们却在这里吗
Once they hand us that diploma we're done here
你怎么会觉得我们能毕业
What makes you think we're getting diplomas
就一个问题 伯克利有球队吗
On question,does Berkeley play?
我们准备下学期11月打败那个什么红鹰队
We're scheduled to kick some Red hawk butt next November.
又要开始比赛了
Game on hoops.
又夺了球 最后一投
Oh! One more steal. The final point.
丹弗斯 波顿 离开球场快回到台上
Danforth! Bolton! You get out there and you get onstage!
我从没想过我爸会说这话
I never thought I'd hear my dad say that.
我们在一起
We're all in this together
当我知道
Once we know
我们都是明星
That we are we're all stars
我们了解到
And we see that
东高的老师
East High is a place
鼓励我们打破现状
Where teachers encouraged us to break the status quo.
成就我们自己的选择
And define ourselves as we choose.
运动员会烤法式忌司布丁
Where a jock can cook up a mean creme brulee.
学术天才们能歌善舞
And the brainiac can break down on the dance floor.
在此地...只要选择对的人...
It's a place where one person...if it's the right person...
...我们的一切就随之改变
...Changes us all.
东高让我们拥有终身的挚友
East High is having friends that we'll keep for the rest of our lives.
我想这就意味着我们真正地成为了一体
And I guess that means we really are all in this together.
因为一日是野猫...
Because once a wildcat...
...终身是野猫
...Always a wildcat.
-说得好 -谢谢
-Yeah man. -Thank you!
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you sir. Thank you very much.
从舞台中心展望毕业日
Looking forward from center stage to graduation day
启动未来的按钮
Time to get the future started
我们将去何方 带着什么 无论什么
What we leave what we take with us no matter what
都将成为我们飞翔的双翅
It's something we're a part of we learned to fly
在一起
Together side by side
我希望以后
I just hope the rest of my life
都能如今天的音乐剧
Will feel as good as my
谁说高中就要过去
High school musical who says we have to let it go
它是人生最美好的部分
It's the best part we've ever known
一步走向未来
Step into the future
让我们继续高中音乐剧
But hold on to high school musical
让我们庆祝我们的母校
Let's celebrate where we come from
所有一路相伴的朋友
The friends who've been there all along just like
就像高中音乐剧
A high school musical
没有准备的即兴演出 随心而动
Improvisation without a script no one's written it
现在我们有机会
And now we have the chance to
但是将来某日回顾往昔
But someday we'll be looking back memories we'll have
我们会记得所唱的所有歌
All the songs that we lived through
最美好的时光 不能丢弃
The best of times so why leave them behind
让我们将来的路
Why can't the rest of my life
都与高中音乐剧般精彩
Be like my high school musical
谁说高中生活要结束
Who says we have to let it go
它是人生最美好的部分
It's the best part we've ever known
一步步走向未来
Step into the future
让我们继续高中音乐剧
But hold on to high school musical
让我们为我们的高中庆祝
Let's celebrate where we come from
所有一路相伴的朋友
The friends who've been there all along that's right
我们最终花了点时间认识到
Now we finally realize
我们应该成为怎样的人
Who we are it just took some time
我们生活我们学习来了解真理
We had to live and to learn to see the truth
学习了解真理
Learn to see the truth
未来万事皆可能 我们都自由
That nothing's ever impossible into the future we all free fall
但是我们高中生活将永远继续下去
But forever we'll always have high school
聚会的时间 让我们庆祝
Time to party now celebrate
世界是一个大舞台
Because the world's one big stage
你想要的角色就可能
Any part you want can be yours
每个人歌唱
Everybody sing
演出永远持续下去
But the show is never going to close
我们因此在这里 我们明白
It's what got us here we know
高中生活将永远继续
High School lives on forever more
-高中 -高中音乐剧
-High school -High school musical
高中音乐剧
High school musical
谁说高中生活要结束
Who says we have to let it go
它是人生最美好的部分
It's the best part we've ever known
一步步走向未来
Step into the future but hold on to
让我们继续高中音乐剧
High school musical
-让我们为我们的高中庆祝 -庆祝
-Let's celebrate where we come from -Celebrate
所有一路相伴的朋友
The friends who've been there all along
-是啊 -我希望我的生活就像
-Oh yeah -I wish my life could be like a
高中音乐剧
High school musical
谁说高中生活要结束
Who says we have to let it go
它是人生最美好的部分
It's the best part we've ever known
一步步走向未来
Step into the future but hold on to
让我们继续高中音乐剧
High school musical
让我们为我们的高中庆祝
Let's celebrate where we come from
在一起 生活更美好
All together makes it better
永永远远的记忆
Memories that last forever
我希望我的将来依如
I want the rest of my life to feel just like a
高中音乐剧般精彩
High school musical
高中音乐剧
谁说高中生活要结束
Who says we have to let it go
它是人生最美好的部分
It's the best part we've ever known
一步步走向未来
Step into the future but hold on to
让我们继续高中音乐剧
High school musical
让我们为我们的高中庆祝
Let's celebrate where we come from
在一起 生活更美好
All together makes it better
永永远远的记忆
Memories that last forever
我希望我的将来
I want the rest of my life to
依如
Feel just like a
高中音乐剧般精彩
High school musical!
曾几何时
Remember that time
我也听到过那些话语
I've heard those words before
但现在从我口中说出
But now they're mine
每一缕阳光的温暖记忆
Every memory of the sweet sunshine
洒满了我的心田
Is living here in my heart and mine
每一次微笑
Every laugh
我们一起分享
We share together yeah we still give back
你能相信我们一起的欢乐多么巨大
Can you believe all the fun we've had
准备好接受人生的另一半
Just getting ready for the other half
一个相知朋友成为了知己
You know a friend becomes a part of you
成为了你的一部分
Part of you
就像梦想终于实现
Like this dream is finally coming true
美梦终于成真
Coming true
太美好了 这一切
It's all good alright
一句再见不等于后会无期
See ya later doesn't mean goodbye
因为没有结束 该到飞翔的时刻
'Cause it ain't over there's time to fly
翱翔的时刻
Time to fly
-人生只是开始 -刚刚开始
-And we're just getting started -Just getting started
刚刚开始
Just getting started
让我们庆祝
Let's celebrate
人生即将拉开序幕 我满心期望
Life is coming yeah and I can't wait
这是每个人都要上去的舞台
It's a ride that all of us get to take
我们互相帮助找到方向
We're gonna help each other find our way
停 停 停
Cut cut cut.
伙伴们 伙伴们
Guys! Guys!
我们忘记裤子了
We forgot our pants.
快走 伙伴们
Guys go!
真棒 我不记得我说了什么
Oh perfect! Good! I don't know what I just said.
你们在干什么 三 四...我喜欢
What are you doing Three four...I like it!
...六 七 八
...Six seven eight.
你好 特洛伊
Hi Troy!
-我的灯掉了 -停
-My light just fell. -Cut.
我的天
Oh my gosh.
马克
Mark!
太美好了 这一切
It's all good alright
一句再见不等于后会无期
See ya later doesn't mean
-不等于后会无期 -不等于后会无期
-It don't mean goodbye -It don't mean goodbye
飞翔的时间到了
There's time to fly
人生只是开始
And we're just getting started
太美好了 这一切
It's all good alright
世界在变化 这不奇怪
The world is changing that ain't no surprise
但不能阻止我们飞翔
But that can't stop us just let it fly
人生只是开始
'Cause we're just getting started
太美好了 这一切...
It's all good alright...
回想当初
Take it back to the place when you know it all began
我们可以随意扮演任何角色
We could be anything we wanna be
喧嚣声中 当年的那群孩子又回来了
We can tell by the noise that the boys are back again
一起来刷新历史
Together making history
是时候展示
It's time to show how
如何成为超级英雄
To be a superhero
就像与
Just like a showdown
威尔史密斯还有劳勃狄尼洛挑战
Will Smith and Bobby De Niro
毋庸置疑我们是最棒的
We're the best no doubt
和以前一样
Doing it like we used to do
这是我们的地盘
This is our town
我要告诉你们的是
And I'm telling you oh
我们又回来了 没错
The boys are back hey the boys are back that's right
我们又回来了 和以前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
把邻居们都吵醒
Gonna wake up the neighborhood
我们又回来了　我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back all right
随心所欲的爬墙
Climbing up the walls any time we want
不必啰嗦 我们又回到了从前
The word is out the boys are back
我们又回来了
The boys are back
回来拯救世界
Back to save the day
不必啰嗦 我们又回到了从前
The boys are back the word is out the boys are back
回来改变世界
Here to change the world
揭开谜团 挺身而战
To solve the mystery fight the battle
拯救自己心爱的女孩
Save the girl
我们势不可挡
No one no one can stop us now
规则由我们掌控
We're the ones that make the rules
我们又回来了 我们又回来了
The boys are back hey the boys are back that's right
我们又回来了 和以前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
把邻居们吵醒
Gonna wake up the neighborhood
我们又回来了 我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back all right
随心所欲的爬墙
Climbing up the walls any time we want
毋庸担心 因为...
No need to worry 'cause...
我们又回来了 我们又回来了
The boys are back hey the boys are back look out now
我们又回来了 和从前一样
The boys are back gonna do it again
我们让一切变得更好
And we make it look good
我们又回来了 我们又回来了
The boys are back yeah the boys are back
随意粉碎阻挡我们的高墙
Tearing down the walls any time we want
我想你们现在该明白了
I'm sure that you know by now
我们又回来了
The boys are back